{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Bulworth",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty produced Bulworth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6626551747322083,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49616482853889465,
            "question": "When was the movie Bulworth released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4564516842365265,
            "question": "Was Bulworth a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4134924113750458,
            "question": "What other movies has Warren Beatty produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3993208408355713,
            "question": "What is Warren Beatty known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3442099988460541,
            "question": "Is Warren Beatty an actor, director, or producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34151747822761536,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28394773602485657,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2000425010919571,
            "question": "What are some of Warren Beatty's most famous roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15896964073181152,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Warren Beatty's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty produced Bulworth.",
            "html": "yago_21506_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Warren Beatty's most famous roles?",
            "html": "yago_21506_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Bulworth?",
            "html": "yago_21506_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who starred in the movie Bulworth?",
            "html": "yago_21506_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21506_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Warren Beatty co-produced the film \"Bulworth,\" which supports the statement that Warren Beatty produced \"Bulworth.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}